const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":1,
    "question":"When you climb outside playing loud music is:",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"Not Cool",
      "B":"Distracting",
      "C":"An element of Risk",
      "D":"All of the above"
    }],
    "correct":"All of the above"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":2,
    "question":"First step to do before climbing outside:",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"Get aquainted to the area",
      "B":"Buy a guidebook",
      "C":"Post on facebook about it",
      "D":"Nothing"
    }],
    "correct":"Get aquainted to the area"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":3,
    "question":"When you climb outside you should always:",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"Go with someone",
      "B":"Pack sandwiches",
      "C":"Post about it on instagram",
      "D":"None of the above"
    }],
    "correct":"Go with someone"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":4,
    "question":"The main difference between climbing inside vs outside is:",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"Outside is harder",
      "B":"Outside routes are not marked",
      "C":"Outside is more dangerous",
      "D":"More people outside"
    }],
    "correct":"Outside routes are not marked"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":5,
    "question":"What is not allowed outside?",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"Chalk",
      "B":"Brushing",
      "C":"Taping Holds as markers",
      "D":"Stick cliping"
    }],
    "correct":"Taping Holds as markers"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":6,
    "question":"Most common type of hold outside",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"Crimps",
      "B":"Slopers",
      "C":"Pinches",
      "D":"none of the above"
    }],
    "correct":"none of the above"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":7,
    "question":"What are three items required to go sport climbing outside",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"shoes, helmet, quickdraws",
      "B":"belay-device, rope, quickdraws",
      "C":"cd-player, peanuts, water",
      "D":"rope, cheetos, water"
    }],
    "correct":"belay-device,rope,quickdraws"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":8,
    "question":"Which best describes climbing outside",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"Easy",
      "B":"Hard",
      "C":"Dangerous",
      "D":"Skin Shredder"
    }],
    "correct":"Skin Shredder"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":9,
    "question":"Which is not a climbing term",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"slimper",
      "B":"Gri-gri",
      "C":"Venga",
      "D":"cheetos"
    }],
    "correct":"cheetos"
  },
  {
    "status":"hidden",
    "number":10,
    "question":"When leaving a crag you must:",
    "answers":[{
      "A":"Post on facebook",
      "B":"Post on instagram",
      "C":"Dance",
      "D":"Leave no trace behind"
    }],
    "correct":"Leave no trace behind"
  },


]
